thankyousearch.com 2009-05-11

# Welcome to ThankYouSearch!

ThankYouSearch does not collect personally identifying information from users of the Services unless users have explicitly given such information to ThankYouSearch (for example, when subscribing to a newsletter or when sending us an email with a question). ThankYouSearch’s information practices are further described in its privacy policy. ThankYouSearch's privacy policy is part of this Agreement, and you agree that use of data as described in the privacy policy is not an actionable breach of your privacy or publicity rights. If you have entered into another agreement with ThankYouSearch (such as a Partner Agreement or a Merchant Agreement), then you may be subject to additional or different provisions regarding privacy and data collection. If you would like more information, please read our privacy policy. 

You should consider any communication that you transmit to ThankYouSearch (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that ThankYouSearch will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient. 

###  Control over Features, Functions, and Access to the Services 

ThankYouSearch reserves the right to change any information, features and functions of the Services without prior notice. ThankYouSearch may deny you access to all or part of the Services without prior notice if you engage in any conduct or activities that ThankYouSearch determines, in its sole discretion, violate this Agreement, the rights of ThankYouSearch or any third party, or is otherwise inappropriate. 

###  Choice of Law, Waiver, and Claims 

This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions. ThankYouSearch’s failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Agreement will not be deemed to be a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of this Agreement is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties' intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of this Agreement remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of the Services must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. 

###  Arbitration 

Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement or the Services will be settled by binding arbitration in accordance with the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association. Any such controversy or claim must be arbitrated on an individual basis, and must not be consolidated in any arbitration with any claim or controversy of any other party. The arbitration must be conducted in Los Angeles, California, and judgment on the arbitration award may be entered into any court having jurisdiction thereof. Either you or ThankYouSearch may seek any interim or preliminary relief from a court of competent jurisdiction in Los Angeles, California, as necessary to protect the rights or property of you or ThankYouSearch. 

###  Notice 

You may direct any questions concerning this Agreement to: 

Legal Affairs   
ThankYouSearch

E-Mail: legal@ThankYouSearch

###  Amendment 

ThankYouSearch may amend this Agreement at any time by posting the amended terms on its Web site. Except as stated below, all amended terms are automatically effective 7 days after they are initially posted. This Agreement may not be otherwise amended except in a written document signed by you and ThankYouSearch. 

This agreement was last revised on January 18, 2008. 

###  ThankYouSearch Privacy Commitment 

At ThankYouSearch we appreciate your privacy and hope that you feel comfortable trusting us. We make every effort to keep your information confidential and protect your privacy when using our site and services. We take your privacy and our responsibility under the data protection legislation very seriously. 

###  Collecting Your Information 

ThankYouSearch does not automatically collect any personal information about you. 

###  Cookies 

ThankYouSearch uses cookies, a small text file containing a unique string of numbers or letters that is placed on a computer, to ‘remember’ your computer when you visit the site. Using cookies helps us serve ads, take polls and manage the services we offer. This will not collect any personally identifiable information about you. Cookies do not recognize you as a person, just your computer. They cannot be used to obtain other information from your hard disk. If you need to block cookies this can be done by changing your browser settings. It may help to contact your ISP for assistance. 

###  Third Party Advertising 

The ThankYouSearch website includes ads delivered by third party partners. When you visit the site, information such as the number of times you have viewed an advertisement, but NOT your name, address or other personal information, is used to deliver ads to you. 

###  Third Party Cookies 

In order to deliver advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you need to block cookies this can be done by changing your browser settings. It may help to contact your ISP for assistance. 

###  Disclosing Information 

Personal information and information relating to use of our services, is administered by ThankYouSearch. ThankYouSearch does not lease, sell, or share your personal information. If you contact ThankYouSearch, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your email address. ThankYouSearch may need to disclose personal information when required by law. 

###  Advertising 

ThankYouSearch may use third party service providers to serve ads and emails on our behalf. 

###  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

ThankYouSearch may update this policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. It is recommended that you read the Terms of Use if using the ThankYouSearch site. 

###  Contact Us 

If you would like to contact ThankYouSearch regarding privacy or any other matter please direct your questions to: 

E-Mail: legal@ThankYouSearch
